[
    {
        "udp": "1.1",
        "question": "Hello, Tactica",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9611.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.1",
        "question": "Hello, Tektika",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9611.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.2",
        "question": "Zoom into the UAE.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11256.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial ports in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/3_scenario_1_maltida.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial quotes in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/3_scenario_1_maltida.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.3",
        "question": "What are the commercial pots in the UAE?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/3_scenario_1_maltida.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Khalifa Port Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15537.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Khalifa Port Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15537.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.4",
        "question": "Zoom into Kalifaport Economic Zone",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15537.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.5",
        "question": "For the ships currently here, What is their  vessel movement for the last 24 hours?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_8798.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the port itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4502.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the pot itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4502.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.6",
        "question": "Zoom into the pod itself",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_4502.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.7",
        "question": "Enhance the optical imagery and detect all ships",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5676.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.7",
        "question": "Inhale the optical imagery and detect all shapes.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_5676.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What assets are in the port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What acids are in the pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What acids are in the port?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.8",
        "question": "What assets are in the pot?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14376.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.9",
        "question": "How many staff and visitors are within the port area?  ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12417.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.10",
        "question": "What is the water depth in the port area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15544.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.11",
        "question": "Provide a 3D visualization of the port's underwater topography",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10336.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": -2,
        "question": "Alert",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18747.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.12",
        "question": "Yes, get the image",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1228.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.13",
        "question": "What is the latest known information about this ship?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15160.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.14",
        "question": "What is the trajectory of this ship?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9890.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.15",
        "question": "Open and analyse the new image\nDetect and identify the ships new location and any other suspected activity of the ship",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_8993.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.16",
        "question": "Generate a report on these two ships and send it to Khalid",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_2850.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.17",
        "question": "Yes. Also open the report.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11829.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.18",
        "question": "Close the report.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10241.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.19",
        "question": "Yes,  Lets look at the urban areas of Abu Dhabi, Zoom into Khalifa City and do land cover classification.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_9865.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.20",
        "question": "What are the newly constructed buildings in Khalifa City in 2024?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_3670.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.21",
        "question": "How many vehicles are in the imagery in this area?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_300.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.22",
        "question": "Identify all palm trees in the region and surrounding main roads.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1996.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.23",
        "question": "Run red weevil analysis on the palm trees.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_10697.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.24",
        "question": "What is the current traffic density around the region?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_1297.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.25",
        "question": "Zoom into Zayed airport?",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17377.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.26",
        "question": "Identify all airplanes and what is their operational activity.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_11196.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.27",
        "question": "Identify all A380 airplanes in the airport.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12028.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.28",
        "question": "Zoom into the one connected to the terminal.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_13431.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.29",
        "question": "Run model logic analysis on the airplane.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_18691.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.30",
        "question": "Generate a 3D of the Airbus A380",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_16419.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.31",
        "question": "Do you have high frequency imagery over the airport?  ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_19300.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.32",
        "question": "What are the changes in the western runway over the last 1 hour",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_12377.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.33",
        "question": "Put and explain the thermal imagery.",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_14721.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.34",
        "question": "Standby",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_15823.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.35",
        "question": "What kind of data can the system support? ",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17461.mp3"
    },
    {
        "udp": "1.36",
        "question": "Open the notification tab",
        "answer": "audios/matilda/1_17452.mp3"
    }
]